(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],{16:function(e,t,n){e.exports={SideDrawer:"SideDrawer_SideDrawer__3Oaug",permanent:"SideDrawer_permanent__1gMC4",open:"SideDrawer_open__1FZ6w",close:"SideDrawer_close__2QzPz",navLink:"SideDrawer_navLink__1r4sF",home:"SideDrawer_home__1ud_f",appear:"SideDrawer_appear__2sdQk"}},19:function(e,t,n){e.exports={Container:"Home_Container__21aYr",Body:"Home_Body__1AT-5",body:"Home_body__1itaJ",base:"Home_base__3bnfJ",tests:"Home_tests__1C9Z-",logo:"Home_logo__2-RXw"}},2:function(e,t,n){e.exports={circle:"Option_circle__1zgqD",container:"Option_container__2M6KW",inner:"Option_inner__359Ex",incInner:"Option_incInner__1M0qa",slim:"Option_slim__2ttIS",containerSnippet:"Option_containerSnippet__1TxAH",selected:"Option_selected__lO9PC",inlineBlock:"Option_inlineBlock__2T0S_",false:"Option_false__3H8tU",true:"Option_true__3tScM",option:"Option_option__3OfOt"}},20:function(e,t,n){e.exports={question:"Question_question__1k2_y",options:"Question_options__2_mWs",container:"Question_container__3zG7R",option:"Question_option__omjvf",cover:"Question_cover__26TVz",rightSide:"Question_rightSide__3s7Kq"}},266:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),o=n.n(a),r=n(55),i=n.n(r),s=n(27),c=n(29),l=(n(42),{isOpen:!1}),p=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:l;switch((arguments.length>1?arguments[1]:void 0).type){case"OPEN SIDE DRAWER":return{isOpen:!0};case"CLOSE SIDE DRAWER":return{isOpen:!1}}return e},h=n(10),u=n(11),d=n(13),m=n(12),f=n(14),g=n(8),w=n(15),_=n(28),v=n.n(_),y=n(19),b=n.n(y),E=function(){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:b.a.body},o.a.createElement("img",{src:v.a,alt:"logo",className:b.a.logo}),o.a.createElement("div",{className:b.a.Body},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Welcome to the quiz website for the ECX Front End Track.",o.a.createElement("br",null),"This is just a way to revise what you have learnt so far.")),o.a.createElement("div",{className:b.a.base},o.a.createElement("div",{className:b.a.tests},o.a.createElement(g.b,{to:"/week-one",exact:!0},"Week 1"),o.a.createElement("br",null),o.a.createElement(g.b,{to:"/week-two",exact:!0},"Week 2"),o.a.createElement(g.b,{to:"/week-three",exact:!0},"Week 3"),o.a.createElement(g.b,{to:"/week-four",exact:!0},"Week 4"))),o.a.createElement("footer",null,"Built by Irene and Akin"))},k=[{question:"Which of these is not necessary for front-end web development?",option:["Web Browser","Code Editor","A Computer","Anaconda"],answerIndex:3},{question:"What department is tasked with turning a UI design into code?",option:["UI/UX","Front-End","Dev-Ops","Back-End"],answerIndex:1},{question:"Which of these is the odd one out?",option:["PHP","HTML","JavaScript","CSS"],answerIndex:0},{question:"Which of these is responsible for adding styles to a webpage?",option:["GO","Python","CSS","JavaScript"],answerIndex:2},{question:"The programming language of the web is?",option:["Go","Python","Ruby","Java Script"],answerIndex:3}],O=[{question:"What is the full meaning of HTML?",option:["HYPER TEXT MARKED LANGUAGE","HYPER TEXT MARKUP LANGUAGE","HIGH TEXT MARKED LANGUAGE","HIGH TEXT MARKUP LANGUAGE"],answerIndex:1},{question:"Which one of these represents the head of a HTML document",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:["<h1></h1>","<html></html>","<head></head>","<header></header>"],answerIndex:2},{question:"Which of these is the correct way to write HTML attributes?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:['<h1 style"=color:red;"></h1>','<h1 style="color:red;"></h1>','<h1 style:"color"="red;"></h1>',"<h1 style:\"color:'red';\"></h1>"],answerIndex:1},{question:"Which of these is the odd one out",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:["<h7></h7>","<h6></h6>","<h8></h8>","<h></h>"],answerIndex:1},{question:"Where is the page title that shows in the browser tab defined?",option:["In the head tag","In the body tag","Right above the Document type","In the footer"],answerIndex:0},{question:"How do you define a paragraph in HTML?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:["<paragraph></paragraph>","<q></q>","<p></p>","<p><p/>"],answerIndex:2},{question:"Which of these is the correct way to write multiple HTML attributes?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:['<h1 style"=color:red; font-size: 40px;"></h1>','<h1 style="color:red; font-size: 40px"></h1>','<h1 style:"color"="red"; "font-size"="40px"></h1>',"<h1 style:\"color:'red'; font-size:'40px'\"></h1>"],answerIndex:1},{question:"Which of these is the correct way to make a superscript?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:["<super></super>",'<p style="super"></p>',"<h1 style:super></h1>","<sup></sup>"],answerIndex:3}],x=[{question:'How would you add a quote " " to a text?',type:"snippet",language:"html",option:["<blockquote>I am a quote</blockquote",'<p style="quote">I am a quote</p>',"<q>I am a quote</q>","<quote></quote>"],answerIndex:2},{question:"what is placed in the cite attribute in a blockquote?",option:["The person who said it","Nothing","cite isn't used in blockquote","A link to the original quote"],answerIndex:3},{question:"Which of these is the correct way to write an abbreviation?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:['<abbreviation title="World Health Organisation">WHO</abbreviation>','<abbr title="World Health Organisation">WHO</abbr>','<abb title="World Health Organisation">WHO</abb>','<abbreviation name="World Health Organisation">WHO</abbreviation>'],answerIndex:1},{question:"Why is it important to comment your code?",option:["To make your code more understandable","To make your code run faster","To make your code cleaner","To speed up code execution"],answerIndex:0},{question:"What is the maximum value any of the colors can have in rgb(10, 20, 30)",option:["100","225","125","255"],answerIndex:3},{question:'What does the "a" in "rgba" define?',option:["border","hue","opacity","light intensity"],answerIndex:2},{question:"Which of these is the correct way to make a red heading with a border round it?",type:"snippet",language:"css",option:["h1 {color: red;\nborder: 1px solid}","h1 {color: red;\nborder: solid red}","h1 {color: red;\nborder-right: solid red}"],answerIndex:0}],S=[{question:"What is the full meaning of CSS?",option:["Comparable Style Selectors","Colorful Seperate Styles","Cascading Style Sheets","Creative Style Selectors"],answerIndex:2},{question:"What is the correct way to link a stylesheet in the html?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:['<link rel="stylesheet" href="style.css">','<style rel="stylesheet" href="style.css">','<link to="index.html" rel="stylesheet" href="style.css" type="external">','<a src="style.css">'],answerIndex:0},{question:"Which of these selectors will style all paragraphs to have a font color of red ?",type:"snippet",language:"css",option:["p \n{\n  font-color:red; \n}","para \n{\n  text-color:red; \n}","p \n{\n  color:red; \n}","paragraph \n{\n  font-color:red; \n}"],answerIndex:2},{question:"Which of the following has the highest specificity?",type:"snippet",language:"css",option:["p { \n  /*code goes here*/\n }","p.red { \n  /*code goes here*/\n }","#red{ \n  /*code goes here*/\n }","p#red{ \n  /*code goes here*/\n }"],answerIndex:3},{question:"Which of these will make an element take up the full size available?",type:"snippet",language:"css",option:["display:full;","display:full-size;","display:block;","display:100%;"],answerIndex:2},{question:"What is the corrrect order for styling links?",type:"snippet",language:"css",option:["a:link {\n      color: red;\n  }\n  a:visited {\n      color: green;\n  }\n  a:hover {\n      color: hotpink;\n  }\n  \n  a:active {\n      color: blue;\n  }","a:active {\n    color: red;\n}\na:visited {\n    color: green;\n}\na:hover {\n    color: hotpink;\n}\n\na:link {\n    color: blue;\n}","a:active {\n  color: red;\n}\na:visited {\n  color: green;\n}\na:link {\n  color: hotpink;\n}\n\na:hover {\n  color: blue;\n}","a:visited {\n  color: red;\n}\na:link {\n  color: green;\n}\na:hover {\n  color: hotpink;\n}\n\na:active {\n  color: blue;\n}"],answerIndex:0},{question:"CSS grows quickly",option:["Nay","Yay"],answerIndex:1}],q=n(30),I=n.n(q),W=function(e){function t(){var e,n;Object(h.a)(this,t);for(var a=arguments.length,o=new Array(a),r=0;r<a;r++)o[r]=arguments[r];return(n=Object(d.a)(this,(e=Object(m.a)(t)).call.apply(e,[this].concat(o)))).state={isOpen:!1},n.toggleSide=function(){var e=n.state.isOpen,t=n.props,a=t.open,o=t.close;e?(o(),n.setState({isOpen:!1})):(a(),n.setState({isOpen:!0}))},n}return Object(f.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:I.a.header,id:"head"},o.a.createElement("img",{src:v.a,alt:"logo",className:I.a.Logo}),o.a.createElement("div",{className:I.a.hamBurger,onClick:this.toggleSide,onKeyPress:this.toggleSide,tabIndex:0,role:"button"},o.a.createElement("div",null),o.a.createElement("div",null),o.a.createElement("div",null)))}}]),t}(a.Component),C=n(4),N=n.n(C),H=n(16),A=n.n(H),T=function(e){var t=e.isOpen,n=e.close,a=e.permanent,r=void 0!==a&&a;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"".concat(A.a.SideDrawer," ").concat(t?A.a.open:A.a.close," ").concat(r?A.a.permanent:"")},o.a.createElement("ul",null,ee.map(function(e){var t=e.pathname,a=e.hash,r=e.name;return o.a.createElement("li",{key:r},o.a.createElement(g.b,{to:{pathname:t,hash:a},className:"home"===r?A.a.home:A.a.navLink,onClick:n,exact:!0},r))})))};T.defaultProps={close:N.a.func,permanent:!1};var j=T,L=n(20),D=n.n(L),R=n(270),P=n(269),G=n(2),z=n.n(G),B=function(e){function t(){var e;return Object(h.a)(this,t),(e=Object(d.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).call(this))).selected=function(t,n){t!==n?e.setState({circleClass:"".concat(z.a.circle," ").concat(z.a.slim),innerClass:"".concat(z.a.inner," ").concat(z.a.incInner),containerCLass:"".concat(z.a.container," ").concat(z.a.false),snippetClass:"".concat(z.a.containerSnippet," ").concat(z.a.false)}):e.setState({circleClass:"".concat(z.a.circle," ").concat(z.a.slim),innerClass:"".concat(z.a.inner," ").concat(z.a.incInner),containerCLass:"".concat(z.a.container," ").concat(z.a.true),snippetClass:"".concat(z.a.containerSnippet," ").concat(z.a.true)})},e.state={circleClass:z.a.circle,innerClass:z.a.inner,containerCLass:z.a.container,snippetClass:z.a.containerSnippet},e}return Object(f.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this,t=this.state,n=t.circleClass,a=t.innerClass,r=t.containerCLass,i=t.snippetClass,s=this.props,c=s.option,l=s.type,p=void 0===l?"text":l,h=s.answer,u=s.language;return o.a.createElement("div",null,"text"===p?o.a.createElement("div",{className:r,onClick:this.selected.bind(this,c,h),onKeyPress:this.selected,role:"button",tabIndex:0},o.a.createElement("div",{className:n},o.a.createElement("div",{className:a})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:z.a.option},c)):"snippet"===p&&o.a.createElement(R.a,{className:i,language:u,showLineNumbers:!0,style:P.a,onClick:function(){return e.selected(c,h)}},c))}}]),t}(a.Component);B.defaultProps={type:"text",language:null};var M=B,U=function(e){return e.children},Q=function(e){var t=e.questions;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:D.a.container,id:"test"},o.a.createElement(U,null,o.a.createElement(j,{isOpen:!0,permanent:!0}),o.a.createElement("div",{className:D.a.rightSide},t.map(function(e,t){var n=e.type,a=e.option,r=e.question,i=e.answerIndex,s=e.language;return o.a.createElement(U,{key:a},o.a.createElement("h1",{className:D.a.question,key:a},"".concat(t+1,") "),r),o.a.createElement("div",{className:D.a.options},a.map(function(e){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:D.a.option,key:e},o.a.createElement(M,{option:e,type:n,key:e,answer:a[i],language:s}))})))}))))},J=function(e){function t(e){var n;Object(h.a)(this,t);var a=(n=Object(d.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).call(this,e))).props.isOpen;return n.state={isOpen:a},n}return Object(f.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this.props,t=e.openNav,n=e.closeNav,a=e.isOpen,r=e.week;return o.a.createElement(U,null,o.a.createElement(W,{open:t,close:n}),o.a.createElement(j,{isOpen:a,close:n}),o.a.createElement(Q,{questions:r}))}}]),t}(a.Component),K=Object(c.b)(function(e){return{isOpen:e.isOpen}},function(e){return{openNav:function(){return e({type:"OPEN SIDE DRAWER"})},closeNav:function(){return e({type:"CLOSE SIDE DRAWER"})}}})(J),X=function(){return o.a.createElement(K,{week:k})},F=function(){return o.a.createElement(K,{week:O})},Y=function(){return o.a.createElement(K,{week:x})},Z=function(){return o.a.createElement(K,{week:S})},V=n(61),$=n.n(V),ee=[{pathname:"/",name:"home"},{pathname:"/week-one",hash:"#test",name:"week one"},{pathname:"/week-two",hash:"#test",name:"week two"},{pathname:"/week-three",hash:"#test",name:"week three"},{pathname:"/week-four",hash:"#test",name:"week four"}],te=function(){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:$.a.General},o.a.createElement(w.a,{path:"/",exact:!0,component:E}),o.a.createElement(w.a,{path:"/week-one",component:X}),o.a.createElement(w.a,{path:"/week-two",component:F}),o.a.createElement(w.a,{path:"/week-three",component:Y}),o.a.createElement(w.a,{path:"/week-four",component:Z}))},ne=function(e){function t(){return Object(h.a)(this,t),Object(d.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(f.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return o.a.createElement(g.a,{basename:"/ecx-frontEnd-site"},o.a.createElement("div",null,o.a.createElement(te,null)))}}]),t}(a.Component),ae=Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));function oe(e,t){navigator.serviceWorker.register(e).then(function(e){e.onupdatefound=function(){var n=e.installing;null!=n&&(n.onstatechange=function(){"installed"===n.state&&(navigator.serviceWorker.controller?(console.log("New content is available and will be used when all tabs for this page are closed. See https://bit.ly/CRA-PWA."),t&&t.onUpdate&&t.onUpdate(e)):(console.log("Content is cached for offline use."),t&&t.onSuccess&&t.onSuccess(e)))})}}).catch(function(e){console.error("Error during service worker registration:",e)})}var re=Object(s.b)(p);i.a.render(o.a.createElement(c.a,{store:re},o.a.createElement(ne,null)),document.getElementById("root")),function(e){if("serviceWorker"in navigator){if(new URL("/ecx-frontEnd-site",window.location.href).origin!==window.location.origin)return;window.addEventListener("load",function(){var t="".concat("/ecx-frontEnd-site","/service-worker.js");ae?(function(e,t){fetch(e).then(function(n){var a=n.headers.get("content-type");404===n.status||null!=a&&-1===a.indexOf("javascript")?navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister().then(function(){window.location.reload()})}):oe(e,t)}).catch(function(){console.log("No internet connection found. App is running in offline mode.")})}(t,e),navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(){console.log("This web app is being served cache-first by a service worker. To learn more, visit https://bit.ly/CRA-PWA")})):oe(t,e)})}}()},28:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n.p+"static/media/brand.50e047d0.svg"},30:function(e,t,n){e.exports={header:"Nav_header__2i12B",Logo:"Nav_Logo__y7BAs",hamBurger:"Nav_hamBurger__1z6yJ",stretch1:"Nav_stretch1__2iMXz",stretch2:"Nav_stretch2__1rQko",stretch3:"Nav_stretch3__o1UiA"}},42:function(e,t,n){},61:function(e,t,n){e.exports={General:"routes_General__24boz"}},62:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(266)}},[[62,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.f87e5bdc.chunk.js.map